{
    "name": ".\\Italian\\Italian10.json",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicine",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941374.7161431,
            "question": "La scuola e' vicina. Le scuole sono ___",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "teatro"
            ],
            "answer": "(un) teatro",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941426.5525901,
            "question": "Given the definition \"theater\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "theater",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941403.56042,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"(un) teatro\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "interessanti",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941381.6923735,
            "question": "Il museo e' interessante. I musei sono ___",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicino",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517941437.877129,
            "question": "La farmacia e' qui (near).",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "scusi",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941399.876403,
            "question": "Given the definition \"excuse me (formal)\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "la scuola e' qui vicino"
            ],
            "answer": "La scuola e' qui vicino.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517941444.280092,
            "question": "Given the definition \"The school is nearby.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "lontani",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941434.4093404,
            "question": "L'ospedale e' lontano. Gli ospedali sono ___",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "train station",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517941550.6428733,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"(una) stazione\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicino",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517941542.586263,
            "question": "I supermercati sono (near) alla stazione.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicini",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941457.6954818,
            "question": "L'ufficio postale e' vicino. Gli uffici postali sono ___.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "There is a movie theater on Roma avenue"
            ],
            "answer": "There is a movie theater on Roma Avenue.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517941562.911708,
            "question": "Given the definition \"C'e' un cinema in viale Roma.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "merry christmas"
            ],
            "answer": "Merry Christmas",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941529.209633,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"buon Natale\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "banca, ufficio",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517941546.9503863,
            "question": "The bank and the post office are downtown. La ___ e l'___ postale sono in centro.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "have a good dinner"
            ],
            "answer": "Enjoy your dinner!",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941451.4896243,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Buona cena!\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicine",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941539.5459456,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"near (plural feminine)\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "excellent",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941565.7957046,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"eccelente/eccelenti\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "gentile"
            ],
            "answer": "gentile/gentili",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517941620.9886172,
            "question": "Given the definition \"kind\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "poi",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517941643.4772305,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"then\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicino",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941617.8108857,
            "question": "La stazione e' (near) all abanca.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "close (feminine)"
            ],
            "answer": "near (singular feminine)",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517941633.941365,
            "question": "Given the definition \"vicina\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicino",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941606.6614742,
            "question": "La famracia e' (near) all stazione.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ufficio postale"
            ],
            "answer": "(un) officio postale",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941577.0165846,
            "question": "Given the definition \"post office\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "incrocio",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517941641.6504924,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"intersection\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "a pharmacy"
            ],
            "answer": "pharmacy",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941650.973732,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"(una) farmacia\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "il teatro e' vicino alla chiesa"
            ],
            "answer": "Il teatro e' vicino alla chiesa.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1517941816.7445924,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"The theater is next to the church.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "la scuola e' vicina"
            ],
            "answer": "La scuola e' vicina.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517941787.1424408,
            "question": "Given the definition \"The school is near.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicini",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941746.093191,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"near (plural masculine)\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "hospital"
            ],
            "answer": "the hospital",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941733.1531208,
            "question": "Given the definition \"l'ospedale\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "have a good trip",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941738.6215575,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"buon viaggio\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "second",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517941764.2134743,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"secondo/seconda/secondi/seconde\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Dov'e la stazione?"
            ],
            "answer": "Dov'e' la stazione?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941762.1592286,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Where is the train station?\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "lontane",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517941897.3371696,
            "question": "La banca e' lontana. Le banche sono ___",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "buona passeggiata"
            ],
            "answer": "Buona passeggiata!",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517941905.083171,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Enjoy your walk!\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "first",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941818.6381264,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"primo/prima/primi/prime\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "vicino"
            ],
            "answer": "vicino / vicina / vicini / vicine",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941876.7600546,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"near\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "a restaurant"
            ],
            "answer": "restaurant",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941841.6940694,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"(un) ristorante\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "teatro, piazza",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941851.6432292,
            "question": "And there's a theater in Dante Square. E c'e' un ___ in ___ Dante.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicino",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517941900.4942477,
            "question": "La banca e' qui (near).",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "per",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517941878.4955895,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"through\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "again",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517941992.5942492,
            "question": "Given the definition \"ancora\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la scuola",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517941996.4885983,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the school\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ancora",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517942001.1184874,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"again\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "The school is next to the church"
            ],
            "answer": "The school is next to the church.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941990.1107712,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"La scuola e' vicino alla chiesa.\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "There is a church on Mazzini street"
            ],
            "answer": "There is a church on Mazzini Street.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941979.7002242,
            "question": "Given the definition \"C'e' una chiesa in via Mazzini.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "supermercato"
            ],
            "answer": "(un) supermercato",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517942004.8477952,
            "question": "Given the definition \"supermarket\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "Is there a bank nearby?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941923.0383067,
            "question": "Given the definition \"C'e' una banca qui vicino?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "C'e una banca qui vicino"
            ],
            "answer": "C'e' una banca qui vicino.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517942032.8701656,
            "question": "Given the definition \"There is a bank nearby.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "good luck",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942081.1646805,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"buona fortuna\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the school is nearby"
            ],
            "answer": "The school is nearby.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942073.6210253,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"La scuola e' qui vicino.\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ristorante"
            ],
            "answer": "(un) ristorante",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942090.0930507,
            "question": "Given the definition \"restaurant\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicina",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942084.9160535,
            "question": "La banca e' (near).",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "scusa",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517942123.128345,
            "question": "Given the definition \"excuse me (informal)\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "buona cena"
            ],
            "answer": "Buona cena!",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517942118.3445218,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Enjoy your dinner!\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "secondo"
            ],
            "answer": "secondo/seconda/secondi/seconde",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942076.87678,
            "question": "Given the definition \"second\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "The restaurant is next to the school"
            ],
            "answer": "The restaurant is next to the school.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942102.3138933,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Il ristorante e' vicino alla scuola.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "chiesa, centro",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942236.3916612,
            "question": "The church is downtown, too. Anche la ___ e' in ___.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "il ristorante e' vicino alla scuola"
            ],
            "answer": "Il ristorante e' vicino alla scuola.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942166.9002547,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"The restaurant is next to the school.\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "downtown",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942228.281234,
            "question": "Given the definition \"in centro\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "stazione"
            ],
            "answer": "(una) stazione",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942242.0850985,
            "question": "Given the definition \"train station\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "happy anniversary",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942252.9505417,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"buon anniversario\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "far",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942255.63078,
            "question": "Given the definition \"lontano / lontana / lontani / lontane\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "hospital",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942259.3247063,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"(un) ospedale\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicine",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517942222.8943114,
            "question": "Le scuole sono (near).",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "la scuola e' vicino alla chiesa"
            ],
            "answer": "La scuola e' vicino alla chiesa.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942314.9294984,
            "question": "Given the definition \"The school is next to the church.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "farmacia"
            ],
            "answer": "(una) farmacia",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942296.3527768,
            "question": "Given the definition \"pharmacy\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "C'e una banca qui vicino"
            ],
            "answer": "C'e' una banca qui vicino?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942288.7691653,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Is there a bank nearby?\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "close"
            ],
            "answer": "near",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942318.6213312,
            "question": "Given the definition \"vicino / vicina / vicini / vicine\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "a destra"
            ],
            "answer": "(a) destra",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517942369.7202468,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"on the right, to the right\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the theater is next to the church"
            ],
            "answer": "The theater is next to the church.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942335.0575323,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Il teatro e' vicino alla chiesa.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "buona fortuna",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942274.1208155,
            "question": "Given the definition \"good luck\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "up to",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517942372.6768842,
            "question": "Given the definition \"fino a\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "supermercato"
            ],
            "answer": "un supermercato",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942468.4207935,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"a supermarket\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "traffic light",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942553.968586,
            "question": "Given the definition \"semaforo\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "C'e una chiesa in via Mazzini"
            ],
            "answer": "C'e' una chiesa in via Mazzini.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942488.5534592,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There is a church on Mazzini Street.\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicino",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942549.3267922,
            "question": "L'ufficio postale e' (near).",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "buone feste",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517942575.4742172,
            "question": "Given the definition \"happy holidays\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "happy birthday",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942493.0757034,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"buon compleanno\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sempre diritto",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517942586.4057543,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"straight ahead\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the school is close"
            ],
            "answer": "The school is near.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942474.298371,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"La scuola e' vicina.\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "il museo e' vicino alla stazione"
            ],
            "answer": "Il museo e' vicino alla stazione.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942600.5988865,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"The museum is next to the station.\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "kind",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942609.3559797,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"gentile/gentili\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "close (plural, feminine)"
            ],
            "answer": "near (plural feminine)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942666.4620845,
            "question": "Given the definition \"vicine\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "eccelenti",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942673.020581,
            "question": "La scuola e' eccelente. Le scuole sono ___",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "stazione, vicino, scuola",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942655.41192,
            "question": "The train station is next to the school. La ___ e' ___ alla ___.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "eccelente"
            ],
            "answer": "eccelente/eccelenti",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942620.963402,
            "question": "Given the definition \"excellent\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "chiesa"
            ],
            "answer": "(una) chiesa",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942604.4962778,
            "question": "Given the definition \"church\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "intersection",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942615.4304152,
            "question": "Given the definition \"incrocio\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ospedale"
            ],
            "answer": "(un) ospedale",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942736.427753,
            "question": "Given the definition \"hospital\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "post office",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942728.721307,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"(un) officio postale\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "buon compleanno",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517942739.5767436,
            "question": "Given the definition \"happy birthday\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "lontano"
            ],
            "answer": "lontano / lontana / lontani / lontane",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942711.1322088,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"far\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicina",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942707.4577672,
            "question": "La scuola e' (near).",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "supermarket",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517942755.8937438,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"(un) supermercato\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "excuse me (informal)",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517942751.7034256,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"scusa\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicina",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942714.8970623,
            "question": "La banca e' (near).",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "a sinistra"
            ],
            "answer": "(a) sinistra",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517942801.1689675,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"on the left, to the left\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "straight ahead",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942764.692037,
            "question": "Given the definition \"sempre diritto\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "cinema"
            ],
            "answer": "(un) cinema",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942761.0537403,
            "question": "Given the definition \"movie theater\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "then",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517942797.5779428,
            "question": "Given the definition \"poi\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "left"
            ],
            "answer": "on the left, to the left",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942777.1657767,
            "question": "Given the definition \"(a) sinistra\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "l'ospedale",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517942789.9644554,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the hospital\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "banca"
            ],
            "answer": "(una) banca",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942785.6470091,
            "question": "Given the definition \"bank\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicine",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942793.851476,
            "question": "Le scuole sono (near).",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "in centro",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517942855.761899,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"downtown\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicino",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517942853.389964,
            "question": "Le scuole sono (near) alla banca.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ospedale, lontano",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942841.0263782,
            "question": "The hospital is far. L'___ e' ____.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "semaforo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942833.5940835,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"traffic light\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicina",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942803.9318128,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"near (singular feminine)\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "museo"
            ],
            "answer": "(un) museo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942815.6840053,
            "question": "Given the definition \"museum\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "happy holidays",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942819.3970351,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"buone feste\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "There is a bank nearby"
            ],
            "answer": "There is a bank nearby.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942830.938894,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"C'e' una banca qui vicino.\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "eccelenti"
            ],
            "answer": "eccelelenti",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942866.4624314,
            "question": "Il ristorante e' eccelente. I ristoranti sono ___",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "gentili",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517942910.399024,
            "question": "La madre e' gentile. Le madri sono ___",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "right"
            ],
            "answer": "on the right, to the right",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942879.3693774,
            "question": "Given the definition \"(a) destra\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicino",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942858.861532,
            "question": "Le scuole sono qui (near).",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "have a good walk"
            ],
            "answer": "Enjoy your walk!",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942898.5184333,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Buona passeggiata!\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "simpatici",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942884.4693284,
            "question": "Il padre e' simpatico. I padri sono ___",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicino",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942903.9422922,
            "question": "Gli ospedali sono (near) alla scuola.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "citta'",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517942907.595392,
            "question": "This is my hometown. Questa e' la mia ___ natale.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "farmacia, vicina",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517942993.8586814,
            "question": "The pharmacy, on the other hand, is near. La ___, inceve, e' ___.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "a school"
            ],
            "answer": "school",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942955.6450934,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"(una) scuola\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "The museum is next to the train station"
            ],
            "answer": "The museum is next to the station.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942935.514171,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Il museo e' vicino alla stazione.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "supermarket"
            ],
            "answer": "a supermarket",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517942984.7447598,
            "question": "Given the definition \"un supermercato\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "C'e una farmacia in piazza Dante"
            ],
            "answer": "C'e' una farmacia in piazza Dante.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942950.8151426,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There is a pharmacy in Dante Square.\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicino",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942913.7555523,
            "question": "Il ristorante e' (near) alla farmacia.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "a movie theater"
            ],
            "answer": "movie theater",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942960.3631809,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"(un) cinema\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicino",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942925.7877676,
            "question": "La chiesa e' qui (near).",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "primo"
            ],
            "answer": "primo/prima/primi/prime",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517943030.755168,
            "question": "Given the definition \"first\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "buon riposo",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517943049.0382235,
            "question": "Given the definition \"have a good rest\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicina",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517943026.520067,
            "question": "La famracia e' (near).",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "a bank"
            ],
            "answer": "bank",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517942996.7672567,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"(una) banca\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "buon anniversario",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517943055.1901574,
            "question": "Given the definition \"happy anniversary\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicini",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517943045.2143593,
            "question": "Gli ospedali sono (near).",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicino",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517943010.3949149,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"near (singular masculine)\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "near"
            ],
            "answer": "near (singular masculine)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517943022.273589,
            "question": "Given the definition \"vicino\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "a museum"
            ],
            "answer": "museum",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517943069.9292727,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"(un) museo\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "through",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517943072.9982276,
            "question": "Given the definition \"per\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "un ufficio postale"
            ],
            "answer": "un officio postale",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517943087.4049065,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"a post office\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "close (plural, masculine)"
            ],
            "answer": "near (plural masculine)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517943079.8527038,
            "question": "Given the definition \"vicini\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the school",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517943058.0622406,
            "question": "Given the definition \"la scuola\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Dov'e una cinema in viale Roma?",
                "Dov'e un cinema in viale Roma?"
            ],
            "answer": "C'e' un cinema in viale Roma.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517943160.8430429,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Where is a movie theater on Roma Avenue?\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "a post office",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517943061.264364,
            "question": "Given the definition \"un officio postale\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "a church"
            ],
            "answer": "church",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517943146.6089227,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"(una) chiesa\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Where is the station"
            ],
            "answer": "Where is the train station?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517943232.9245458,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Dov'e' la stazione?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicino",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517943172.2326064,
            "question": "La banca e' (near) alla chiesa.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "have a good rest",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517943227.6975782,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"buon riposo\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "buon viaggio",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517943250.1015816,
            "question": "Given the definition \"have a good trip\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicini",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517943222.4555576,
            "question": "Il semaforo e' vicino. I semafori sono ____",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "excuse me (formal)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517943166.1440709,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"scusi\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "C'e, cinema"
            ],
            "answer": "C'e', cinema",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517943244.4581766,
            "question": "There's a movie theater on Mazzini street. ___ un ___ in via Mazzini.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "buon natale"
            ],
            "answer": "buon Natale",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517943252.7604947,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Merry Christmas\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "C'e una cinema in viale Roma"
            ],
            "answer": "C'e' un cinema in viale Roma.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517943298.7257938,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There is a movie theater on Roma Avenue.\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "There is a pharmacy on Dante plaza"
            ],
            "answer": "There is a pharmacy in Dante Square.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517943276.8033137,
            "question": "Given the definition \"C'e' una farmacia in piazza Dante.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "There is a movie theater on Roma street"
            ],
            "answer": "Where is a movie theater on Roma Avenue?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517943262.7490623,
            "question": "Given the definition \"C'e' un cinema in viale Roma.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "fino a",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517943315.6741748,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"up to\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "scuola"
            ],
            "answer": "(una) scuola",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517943306.1206872,
            "question": "Given the definition \"school\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        }
    ]
}